As the last thing, we'll learn a very
useful method to recycle our data
最后 我们学习一个非常有用的循环利用数据的方法
称为 k 折交叉验证
called k-fold cross validation.
如之前所学 我们将数据分为训练集和测试集
As we have learned, testing is done by
separating our data into a training and
a testing set.
来进行测试
但这并不总是理想的做法 因为我们似乎会扔掉一些
But this is not always ideal as we seem
to be throwing away some data that
could be useful for
training our algorithm.
对训练我们的算法有用的数据
那么有办法可以让我们不用扔掉这些数据
Is there anything we can do
to not throw away this data?
而同时又不用作弊吗？
But at the same time not cheat?
这里有一个解决方法
Well here's the solution, and
this is when K Fold Cross Validation
comes in to play.
也是 K 折交叉验证派上用场的时候
在 K 折交叉验证中 我们将数据分为 K 个包
What we do with K Fold Cross Validation
is to break our data in to K buckets.
在这个例子中 K 等于 4
In this case, K is four.
然后我们将模型培训 K 次
Then we just train our model K times.
每次将不同的包用作测试集
Each time using a different
bucket as our testing set and
而剩下的点作为训练集
the remaining points
as our training set.
然后我们求结果的平均值 来得到最终模型
Then we average the results
to get a final model.
The command to do this in
sklearn is very simple.
在 sklearn 中执行此操作的命令非常简单
All we have to do is
create a KFold object
我们要做的就是创建一个 KFold 对象
where the parameters are the size of the
data and the size of the testing set.
其中参数为数据的大小和测试集的大小
It is always recommended to randomize
our data to remove any hint of a bias.
始终建议随机化我们的数据 以消除任何可能的偏差
Here we are still splitting
our data into buckets,
这里我们仍然将数据拆分为包
except these are chosen
randomly instead of in order.
但是是随机而非顺序选择
在 sklearn 中进行随机化也很容易 只需
Randomizing is also easily
done in sklearn by setting
the shuffle parameter to true when
we initialize our KFold object.
在初始化 KFold 对象时将 shuffle 参数设为 true 即可